<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Achievements on Abir Arsalane</title>
    <link>https://abirarsalane.github.io/achievements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Achievements on Abir Arsalane</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://abirarsalane.github.io/achievements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Distinctions</title>
      <link>https://abirarsalane.github.io/achievements/distinction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abirarsalane.github.io/achievements/distinction/</guid>
      <description>Description I have participated in many events, competitions, hackathons, etc. Here are some of the most important ones.
Alumnus of Mathematics Olympiads Been a mathematics olympiads participant for 5 years, from middle school to high school, while being a national winner in middle school. Attended mentorship sessions and trainings from previous international finalists and Ecole Polytechnique (X) students. Alumnus of Informatics Olympiads Been an informatics olympiads participant for 3 years, while being ranked 1st in my school and 9th in the country in the Castor contest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteering</title>
      <link>https://abirarsalane.github.io/achievements/volunterring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abirarsalane.github.io/achievements/volunterring/</guid>
      <description>Description I like to help when I can. I volunteer a lot. Here are just a few of my volunteering experiences that are dear to me the most.
EMPIMO member and organizer EMPIMO, or the Moroccan IMO Preparation Team, is a large virtual community of students gifted in competitive mathematics whose goal is to spread the culture of IMOs, provide the necessary orientation and resources to participants, maintain the fluidity of communication Olympic news between supervisors and students as well as providing a space for the exchange of questions and supporting any initiative in this context such as the formation of school clubs and the organization of mathematical competitions, forums and conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracurricular Activities</title>
      <link>https://abirarsalane.github.io/achievements/extracurricular-activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abirarsalane.github.io/achievements/extracurricular-activities/</guid>
      <description>Description Having a life outside of classes and contributing to student&amp;rsquo;s life on campus is just as important as your academic performance and grades. Here are just a few of the most recent activities I&amp;rsquo;ve done. I have always been an active student, but I&amp;rsquo;ve only mentionned university extracurricular activities.
Founder &amp;amp; president of Consulting Club Data4Development Collaborated with 2 startups to get 80+ students involved in solving real life use cases using data science.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
